export const quizData = [
    {
        question: "What is 100/4?",
        options: ["25", "12", "100", "4"],
        correctAnswer: "25",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 2 + 2?",
        options: ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
        correctAnswer: "4",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 8 - 2?",
        options: ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
        correctAnswer: "6",
    },
    {
        question: "what is SSR stand for ?",
        options: [
            "service seva reserve",
            "server side rendering",
            "seva service reservation",
            "none of the above",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "server side rendering",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 121 + 12?",
        options: ["313", "134", "133", "36"],
        correctAnswer: "133",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 12 / 2?",
        options: ["3", "14", "5", "6"],
        correctAnswer: "6",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 21 - 12?",
        options: ["3", "4", "5", "9"],
        correctAnswer: "9",
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the co-founder of Matrix Gas",
        options: [
            "Mahak jain",
            "Anmol jaggi",
            "Chirag Kotecha",
            "CS Keval Dave",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Anmol jaggi",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 2 - 2?",
        options: ["3", "0", "5", "6"],
        correctAnswer: "0",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 12 * 2?",
        options: ["24", "2114", "15", "16"],
        correctAnswer: "24",
    },
];
